QIUYAO (CHO) WEI

Madrid, Spain | Cho.q.wei@student.ie.edu | +34 600 292 560 | http://www.linkedin.com/in/giuywei13/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am passionate about product as an enabler to solve complex problems using methodologies such as Agile Scrum with experience in system integration and digital transformation. I am curious, open-minded, and adaptable when dealing with an ambiguous environment that involves a complex web of stakeholders. For my future career path, I am determined to continue my learning with a heavy focus on digital transformation, cloud, and entrepreneurship.

EDUCATION

IE BUSINESS SCHOOL

Madrid, Spain

Master's in Digital Business and Innovation

Expected Jun 2023

• 3.63/4.0 | Scrum Master | Digital Transformation | cloud & product management

Kev Projects

Digital Entrepreneurship Develop MVP for an O2O dining solution using design thinking and product management **UX & CRO** Built a digital product for a boutique chocolate business using UX research tools and agile thinking **Customer-centricity** Develop a loyalty program for Mercadona using customer-centric solution techniques

INDIANA UNIVERSITY, KELLEY SCHOOL OF BUSINESS

Indiana, USA

B.S. in Business Administration, Information Systems; Minor: Spanish

Aug 2014 – Jul 2018

- · Alpha Kappa Psi Business fraternity | Women in Technology | University IT Support
- Spanish study abroad program in Barcelona at Universitat de Vic Universitat Central de Catalunya (2018)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

World Family English, Ltd.

Shanghai, China

Product Owner

Nov 2021 - Nov 2022

- Implemented CRM with a lean team of highly qualified international experts to help local sales and marketing team increase work efficiency by 20% across different systems by integrating customer data on a SaaS platform
- Collaborated with local project manager to collect 18 relevant stakeholders' requirements by conducting daily workshops to understand local business processes, stakeholder journey and user pain points
- Composed over 300 user stories on Jira's product backlog throughout development and testing cycle based on user requests, feedback and observations
- Maintained product backlog and collaborated with Scrum team on sprint backlog to optimize workflow resulting in first value-added MVP launch after 24 weekly sprints of development, testing and deployment

Shanghai Finigate Trading Co. Ltd.

Shanghai, China

Product Manager of Cookie Crew (Boutique soft cookie brand)

May 2020 - Aug 2021

- Utilized Agile methodology to oversee and drive new product development with different functional teams including fundamental activities such as product-market fit research, product vision and strategy alignment, key stakeholder communication, real-time data analysis and flavor testing
- Launched first three main products across 5 stores (online and offline) within 3-month time
- Consolidated product line with OEM factory based on sales forecast analysis and marketing research leading to an overall increase of 84% in sales in Shanghai

PwC Business Consulting (Shanghai) Ltd.

Shanghai, China

IT Risk Consultant

Oct 2018 – Apr 2020

- Coordinated with project managers throughout the project timeline to remodel client's user authorization schemes in SAP systems for more than 100 key users in Finance and HR departments based on individual roles and responsibilities mitigating workplace risk by 80%
- Assisted 4 different senior associates to conduct on-site bi-annual risk-based audit for mainly auto industry clients on ERP systems following ISACA framework to minimize risk from potential threats and vulnerabilities

LANGUAGES

Mandarin (Native), English (Native, ESL/TESOL certified), Spanish (Professional Working Proficiency)

CERTIFICATIONS

Agile Scrum CSPO, AWS Cloud Practitioner, Oracle SQL

SKILLS

Jira | Trello | Miro | Python (Data Analysis & Machine Learning) | Tableau | SAP | Confluence | AWS Cloud